<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">oscad</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Home</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Downloads</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Spoken Tutorials</string>
    <string name="title_section4">Contact us</string>
    <string name="title_section5">FAQs</string>
    <string name="title_section6">Weblinks</string>
    <string name="title_section7">Login</string>
    <string name="title_section8">Textbook companion</string>
    <string name="title_section9">Lab migration</string>
    <string name="title_section10">Workshops</string>
    
    <string name="intro">
       	<p style="text-align: justify; margin-top: 10px; margin-bottom: 5px; margin-left: 20px;"><b>Oscad</b> is an open source EDA tool for circuit design, simulation, analysis and PCB design.  It is an integrated tool built using open source software such as KiCad (<a href="http://www.kicad-pcb.org" title="http://www.kicad-pcb.org">http://www.kicad-pcb.org</a>), Ngspice (<a href="http://ngspice.sourceforge.net/" title="http://ngspice.sourceforge.net/">http://ngspice.sourceforge.net</a>) and Scilab (<a href="http://www.scilab.org/" title="http://www.scilab.org/">http://www.scilab.org</a>).  Oscad is released under GPL.</p>
	</string>
	<string name="features">
	    <![CDATA[
		- Draw circuits using KiCad, create a netlist and simulate using Ngspice.<br>
		- Do PCB design and generate Gerber files using KiCad.<br>
		- Add/Edit device models and subcircuits using the Model Builder and Subcircuit Builder tools.<br>
		- Generate differential equations of analog circuits and solve them through Scilab. This feature is unique to Oscad.<br>
		- Runs on Ubuntu Linux and a few flavours of Windows (XP and 7, at present).]]>
	</string>
	<string name="books">
	    <![CDATA[
		- Oscad: An open source EDA tool for circuit design, simulation, analysis and PCB design - Shroff Publishers and Distributers Pvt. Ltd, June 2013<br>
		- The E-version of the Oscad book, Oscad software, examples and Spoken Tutorials that explain the use of Oscad are available under the links : Downloads (<a href="http://oscad.in/downloads" title="http://oscad.in/downloads">http://oscad.in/downloads</a>) and Spoken Tutorials (<a href="http://oscad.in/resources/tutorials" title="http://oscad.in/resources/tutorials">http://oscad.in/resources/tutorials</a>).
		]]>
	</string>
    
    <string name="text_book_companion">
        <ul><li ><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.oscad.in/textbook-companion-project" title="">Textbook Companion Project</a>]]></li><![CDATA[<br>]]>
		<li ><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.oscad.in/textbook-companion-internship" title="Internship">Internship</a>]]></li><![CDATA[<br>]]>
		<li ><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.oscad.in/textbook-companion-guidelines" title="Guidelines for Coding">Guidelines for Coding</a>]]></li><![CDATA[<br>]]>
		<li ><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.oscad.in/textbook-companion-honorarium" title="">Honorarium</a>]]></li><![CDATA[<br>]]>
		<li ><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.oscad.in/textbook-companion-faqs" title="">Textbook Companion FAQ\'s</a>]]></li><![CDATA[<br>]]>
		<li ><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.oscad.in/completed_books" title="Completed Books">Completed Books</a>]]></li><![CDATA[<br>]]>
		<li ><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.oscad.in/books_progress" title="Books In Progress">Books In Progress</a>]]></li><![CDATA[<br>]]>
		<li ><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.oscad.in/textbook_run">Download Codes</a>]]></li>
		</ul>
    </string>
    
     <string name="FAQs">
        
       If OSCAD is installed on 64 bit Windows XP, there will 
       be a problem launching OSCAD through Start menu. Launch OSCAD through command prompt instead. To do this, open command prompt
        and type the following one after the other:
  
    </string>
    
    <string name="FAQs2">
         - cd \\ &lt;br /&gt;
 	  	 - cd OSCAD\\OSCAD\\forntEnd&lt;br /&gt;
  		 - python oscad.py
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="FAQs3">
        Now Oscad window will open up.
        
     </string>

    
    <string name="FAQs5">
        
        1.  If a footprint library error is displayed on opening Footprint Editor, do the following: 
    </string>
    
      <string name="FAQs4">
    
	    -  On the footprint editor window, click on Preferences and choose Options. &lt;br /&gt;
	
	    -  In the footprint library files section, click on ADD. &lt;br /&gt;
	
	    -  Browse to the path where kicad is installed. Then go to KiCad\share\modules. &lt;br /&gt;
	
	    -  Manually select all the .mod files and click on Open. &lt;br /&gt;
	
	    -  Do the same for KiCad\share\modules\packages3d.
      
      
      
        
    </string>
    
      
      <string name="FAQs6">
          
          

		2. If on launching Ngspice, an error, "System cannot execute the program" occurs, download and install the exe file 
		from <![CDATA[<a href="http://www.microsoft.com/en-us/download/details.aspx?id=29">here</a>]]>  then
		 Relaunch Oscad.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;


   		3. If you are unable to launch KiCad, then uninstall KiCad and install it again in the C directory. For installing, go to Oscad windows installer folder. Go to the folder resources. Double click on the KiCad.exe file. Give the installation path as C:\ After installation, change the environment variable path of Kicad to C:\KiCad\bin.&lt;br /&gt;
          
      </string>
      
      
      
 <string name="text_book">
          
          The Textbook Companion Project (TBC) aims to create Oscad project ﬁles for all the solved
         
          simulation exercises present in standard Electrical and Electronics Engineering textbooks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	   	  The objectives of this project are:
          
      </string>
      
      <string name="text_book2">
          
          	-  To make it easy for users of such textbooks to start using Oscad. &lt;br /&gt;

  			-  To improve the documentation available for Oscad.
      </string>
      
      <string name="text_book3">
          
		The Oscad Textbook Companion project is managed by the FOSSEE project,IIT Bombay.&lt;br /&gt;
		Textbook Companion internship is an internship programme for college 
		students who want to undertake an internship. The project will require a teacher as a mentor.
		The mentor must have taught the specific subject for at least one year. The mentor will guide the student 
		through the project and will be responsible for the intern\'s submissions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
		
		The procedure is as follows:
 		
      </string>
      
      <string name="text_book4">
          1. You should know or learn Oscad. Resources are provided at Oscad Resources. Learning Oscad is easy and 
          if someone listens to and practices the Spoken Tutorials on Oscad, it can be learned in 2-3 days. For use of
           any software package other than Oscad, contact us at textbookcompanion@oscad.in &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

		   2. You should propose three books in the order of your preference, using the proposal 
		   form available here. You have to create a new account and log in to access the proposal form. 
		   You must ensure that the books you are proposing have not been been completed or undertaken under this project. 
		   Click on Completed Books and Books in Progress to see the respective lists.&lt;br /&gt;

			We will try to allot one of the three proposed books to you. Along with the book proposal, you are required to send a 
			typical chapter\'s solved examples project file using Oscad from one of the three proposed books to textbook-companion@oscad.in in a .zip or 
			.tgz file. We will not contact you to send the code. &lt;br /&gt;

			It is suggested that you propose the book as early as possible,
			 and not wait for the last date as your preferred book may be assigned to someone else. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

			3. You will be intimated about the approval or rejection of your proposal via email within 3 days. 
			If you are selected, then your name along with the proposed textbook will appear under Books in Progress. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

			4. After final allotment, you will start creating schematics and perform simulation of 
			only the solved simulation examples from the entire book. You are required to upload the project files on the interface.
			 Also, send the code to your mentor. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

			Note: Lack of regularity on your part may force us to cancel your internship and the book will be assigned
			 to another intern. Simultaneously, you should fill the IITB registration form and post it to us. All the
			  required forms are available at Required Internship Forms. 	&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

			5. The time-frame for completion of the book coding will be decided together by you, your mentor and us.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

			6. Review of the book - The review of the book will typically take approximately 10 days to finish. 
			If any code is found to be not producing the desired result during review process, the student will have to recheck and resubmit all the 
			codes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

			7. Candidates who finish the report as per specified procedures will get an internship 
			certificate: "Certified that the work completed is equivalent to six weeks of training under the supervision of the concerned faculty of IIT Bombay".&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

			8. You will be awarded an honorarium of ₹ 150 per example and your mentor ₹ 100 per example 
			for completing this work. &lt;br /&gt;
          
          
      </string>
      
      
      <string name="guideline">
          
            1. Avoid spaces in project names. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			2. Project name should be same as the example number.(e.g example_2.3) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			3. Give the respective names and values to the elements as given in the book. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			4. Put the plot option at the inputs and outputs. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			5. Use the proper model of the devices as mentioned in the book, if you are unable to find models of device then contact us at textbook-companion@oscad.in. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			6. Once you have completed the project, mail us at textbook-companion@oscad.in with complete details including your name and allotted book. &lt;br /&gt;
          
      </string>
      <string name="Honorarium">
          
          			Please note the following important honorarium details:
          
      </string>
      <string name="Honorarium1" formatted="false">
          
			1. After submission of ALL the projects, the review is to be requested by the student. 
			If ALL the solutions for the solved examples from the proposed book are found to be working satisfactorily at 
			the time of FIRST review, the student and the mentor will get a bonus amount of ₹ 2,000/- and ₹ 1,000/- respectively, 
			in addition to the honorarium of the sum ₹ 150 per examples and ₹ 100 per examples. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			
			2. If more than 5% codes are found to be erroneous during the FIRST review, the honorarium shall be cut to 30% of the 
			original amount, for the mentor and 20% of the original amount , for the student. The student will be asked to submit 
			ALL the codes again after making the necessary corrections. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			
			3. If ANY code is found to be erroneous after the SECOND review, the student shall not receive any amount as honorarium.
			 The proposed book and the uploaded codes shall be deleted from the Textbook Companion database. &lt;br /&gt;
      </string>
      
      <string name="Honorarium2">
          
          	 <![CDATA[<b>Note:</b>]]>&lt;br /&gt;
			On submission of a Textbook Companion, the review process involves several checks including but not limited to:
      </string>
      
        <string name="Honorarium3">
           	  1. Completeness of the project. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				2. Completeness of the book - missing parts (or) sections. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				3. Plagiarism. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				4. ERC and DRC checks.
      </string>
      
        
        <string name="Honorarium4" >
            
            In this regard, we are forced to test EVERY code of EVERY participant thoroughly. Due to many participants, this 
            verification process takes considerable amount of time. Moreover, dispatch of Government money requires approvals 
            from the Dean\'s Office, Accounts Office, etc. which also takes some time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

			Due to the above listed reasons, immediate acceptance of a Textbook Companion and processing of payment is highly impossible.
			 The participants are therefore requested to show some patience. However, if you do not get your money within 
			 45 days after submitting working code, please get in touch with us - we shall be happy to assist you. 
			 If there are problems with the submitted code, naturally, there will be further delays.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
        </string>
   
        
</resources>
