<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">oscad</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Home</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Downloads</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Spoken Tutorials</string>
    <string name="title_section4">Contact us</string>
    <string name="title_section5">FAQs</string>
    <string name="title_section6">Weblinks</string>
    <string name="title_section7">Textbook companion</string>
    <string name="title_section8">Lab migration</string>
    <string name="title_section9">Workshops</string>
    
    <string name="intro">
       	<p style="text-align: justify; margin-top: 10px; margin-bottom: 5px; margin-left: 20px;"><b>Oscad</b> is an open source EDA tool for circuit design, simulation, analysis and PCB design.  It is an integrated tool built using open source software such as KiCad (<a href="http://www.kicad-pcb.org" title="http://www.kicad-pcb.org">http://www.kicad-pcb.org</a>), Ngspice (<a href="http://ngspice.sourceforge.net/" title="http://ngspice.sourceforge.net/">http://ngspice.sourceforge.net</a>) and Scilab (<a href="http://www.scilab.org/" title="http://www.scilab.org/">http://www.scilab.org</a>).  Oscad is released under GPL.</p>
	</string>
	<string name="features">
	    <![CDATA[
		- Draw circuits using KiCad, create a netlist and simulate using Ngspice.<br>
		- Do PCB design and generate Gerber files using KiCad.<br>
		- Add/Edit device models and subcircuits using the Model Builder and Subcircuit Builder tools.<br>
		- Generate differential equations of analog circuits and solve them through Scilab. This feature is unique to Oscad.<br>
		- Runs on Ubuntu Linux and a few flavours of Windows (XP and 7, at present).]]>
	</string>
	<string name="books">
	    <![CDATA[
		- Oscad: An open source EDA tool for circuit design, simulation, analysis and PCB design - Shroff Publishers and Distributers Pvt. Ltd, June 2013<br>
		- The E-version of the Oscad book, Oscad software, examples and Spoken Tutorials that explain the use of Oscad are available under the links : Downloads (<a href="http://oscad.in/downloads" title="http://oscad.in/downloads">http://oscad.in/downloads</a>) and Spoken Tutorials (<a href="http://oscad.in/resources/tutorials" title="http://oscad.in/resources/tutorials">http://oscad.in/resources/tutorials</a>).
		]]>
	</string>
    
    <string name="text_book_companion">
        <ul><li ><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.oscad.in/textbook-companion-project" title="">Textbook Companion Project</a>]]></li><![CDATA[<br>]]>
		<li ><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.oscad.in/textbook-companion-internship" title="Internship">Internship</a>]]></li><![CDATA[<br>]]>
		<li ><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.oscad.in/textbook-companion-guidelines" title="Guidelines for Coding">Guidelines for Coding</a>]]></li><![CDATA[<br>]]>
		<li ><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.oscad.in/textbook-companion-honorarium" title="">Honorarium</a>]]></li><![CDATA[<br>]]>
		<li ><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.oscad.in/textbook-companion-faqs" title="">Textbook Companion FAQ\'s</a>]]></li><![CDATA[<br>]]>
		<li ><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.oscad.in/completed_books" title="Completed Books">Completed Books</a>]]></li><![CDATA[<br>]]>
		<li ><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.oscad.in/books_progress" title="Books In Progress">Books In Progress</a>]]></li><![CDATA[<br>]]>
		<li ><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.oscad.in/textbook_run">Download Codes</a>]]></li>
		</ul>
    </string>
    
     <string name="FAQs">
        
       If OSCAD is installed on 64 bit Windows XP, there will 
       be a problem launching OSCAD through Start menu. Launch OSCAD through command prompt instead. To do this, open command prompt
        and type the following one after the other:
  
    </string>
    
    <string name="FAQs2">
         - cd \\ &lt;br /&gt;
 	  	 - cd OSCAD\\OSCAD\\forntEnd&lt;br /&gt;
  		 - python oscad.py
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="FAQs3">
        Now Oscad window will open up.
        
    </string>

    
    <string name="FAQs5">
        
        1.  If a footprint library error is displayed on opening Footprint Editor, do the following: 
    </string>
    
    <string name="FAQs4">
    
	    -  On the footprint editor window, click on Preferences and choose Options. &lt;br /&gt;
	
	    -  In the footprint library files section, click on ADD. &lt;br /&gt;
	
	    -  Browse to the path where kicad is installed. Then go to KiCad\share\modules. &lt;br /&gt;
	
	    -  Manually select all the .mod files and click on Open. &lt;br /&gt;
	
	    -  Do the same for KiCad\share\modules\packages3d.
    </string>
    
    <string name="FAQs6">
		2. If on launching Ngspice, an error, "System cannot execute the program" occurs, download and install the exe file 
		from <![CDATA[<a href="http://www.microsoft.com/en-us/download/details.aspx?id=29">here</a>]]>  then
		 Relaunch Oscad.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

   		3. If you are unable to launch KiCad, then uninstall KiCad and install it again in the C directory. For installing, go to Oscad windows installer folder. Go to the folder resources. Double click on the KiCad.exe file. Give the installation path as C:\ After installation, change the environment variable path of Kicad to C:\KiCad\bin.&lt;br /&gt;
    </string>
      
 	<string name="text_book">
          The Textbook Companion Project (TBC) aims to create Oscad project ﬁles for all the solved 
          simulation exercises present in standard Electrical and Electronics Engineering textbooks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
	   	  The objectives of this project are:
    </string>
      
    <string name="text_book2">
       	-  To make it easy for users of such textbooks to start using Oscad. &lt;br /&gt;
		-  To improve the documentation available for Oscad.
    </string>
      
    <string name="text_book3">
		The Oscad Textbook Companion project is managed by the FOSSEE project,IIT Bombay.&lt;br /&gt;
		Textbook Companion internship is an internship programme for college 
		students who want to undertake an internship. The project will require a teacher as a mentor.
		The mentor must have taught the specific subject for at least one year. The mentor will guide the student 
		through the project and will be responsible for the intern\'s submissions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
		The procedure is as follows:
   	</string>
      
    <string name="text_book4">
          1. You should know or learn Oscad. Resources are provided at Oscad Resources. Learning Oscad is easy and 
          if someone listens to and practices the Spoken Tutorials on Oscad, it can be learned in 2-3 days. For use of
           any software package other than Oscad, contact us at 
           <![CDATA[<a href=\'mailto:textbook-companion@oscad.in\'>textbookcompanion@oscad.in</a>]]> &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

		   2. You should propose three books in the order of your preference, using the proposal 
		   form available here. You have to create a new account and log in to access the proposal form. 
		   You must ensure that the books you are proposing have not been been completed or undertaken under this project. 
		   Click on Completed Books and Books in Progress to see the respective lists.&lt;br /&gt;

			We will try to allot one of the three proposed books to you. Along with the book proposal, you are required to send a 
			typical chapter\'s solved examples project file using Oscad from one of the three proposed books to 
			<![CDATA[<a href=\'mailto:textbook-companion@oscad.in\'>textbookcompanion@oscad.in</a>]]> in a .zip or 
			.tgz file. We will not contact you to send the code. &lt;br /&gt;

			It is suggested that you propose the book as early as possible,
			 and not wait for the last date as your preferred book may be assigned to someone else. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

			3. You will be intimated about the approval or rejection of your proposal via email within 3 days. 
			If you are selected, then your name along with the proposed textbook will appear under Books in Progress. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

			4. After final allotment, you will start creating schematics and perform simulation of 
			only the solved simulation examples from the entire book. You are required to upload the project files on the interface.
			 Also, send the code to your mentor. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

			Note: Lack of regularity on your part may force us to cancel your internship and the book will be assigned
			 to another intern. Simultaneously, you should fill the IITB registration form and post it to us. All the
			  required forms are available at Required Internship Forms. 	&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

			5. The time-frame for completion of the book coding will be decided together by you, your mentor and us.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

			6. Review of the book - The review of the book will typically take approximately 10 days to finish. 
			If any code is found to be not producing the desired result during review process, the student will have to recheck and resubmit all the 
			codes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

			7. Candidates who finish the report as per specified procedures will get an internship 
			certificate: "Certified that the work completed is equivalent to six weeks of training under the supervision of the concerned faculty of IIT Bombay".&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

			8. You will be awarded an honorarium of ₹ 150 per example and your mentor ₹ 100 per example 
			for completing this work. &lt;br /&gt;
	</string>
      
    <string name="guideline">
            1. Avoid spaces in project names. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			2. Project name should be same as the example number.(e.g example_2.3) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			3. Give the respective names and values to the elements as given in the book. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			4. Put the plot option at the inputs and outputs. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			5. Use the proper model of the devices as mentioned in the book, if you are unable to find models of device then contact us at 
			<![CDATA[<a href=\'mailto:textbook-companion@oscad.in\'>textbookcompanion@oscad.in</a>]]>. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			6. Once you have completed the project, mail us at 
			<![CDATA[<a href=\'mailto:textbook-companion@oscad.in\'>textbookcompanion@oscad.in</a>]]> 
			with complete details including your name and allotted book. &lt;br /&gt;
   	</string>
   	
    <string name="Honorarium">
   			Please note the following important honorarium details:
    </string>
    
    <string name="Honorarium1" formatted="false">
			1. After submission of ALL the projects, the review is to be requested by the student. 
			If ALL the solutions for the solved examples from the proposed book are found to be working satisfactorily at 
			the time of FIRST review, the student and the mentor will get a bonus amount of ₹ 2,000/- and ₹ 1,000/- respectively, 
			in addition to the honorarium of the sum ₹ 150 per examples and ₹ 100 per examples. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			
			2. If more than 5% codes are found to be erroneous during the FIRST review, the honorarium shall be cut to 30% of the 
			original amount, for the mentor and 20% of the original amount , for the student. The student will be asked to submit 
			ALL the codes again after making the necessary corrections. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			
			3. If ANY code is found to be erroneous after the SECOND review, the student shall not receive any amount as honorarium.
			 The proposed book and the uploaded codes shall be deleted from the Textbook Companion database. &lt;br /&gt;
    </string>
      
    <string name="Honorarium2">
          
        <![CDATA[<b>Note:</b>]]>&lt;br /&gt;
		On submission of a Textbook Companion, the review process involves several checks including but not limited to:
   	</string>
      
    <string name="Honorarium3">
           	1. Completeness of the project. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			2. Completeness of the book - missing parts (or) sections. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			3. Plagiarism. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			4. ERC and DRC checks.
     </string>
        
     <string name="Honorarium4" >
            In this regard, we are forced to test EVERY code of EVERY participant thoroughly. Due to many participants, this 
            verification process takes considerable amount of time. Moreover, dispatch of Government money requires approvals 
            from the Dean\'s Office, Accounts Office, etc. which also takes some time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

			Due to the above listed reasons, immediate acceptance of a Textbook Companion and processing of payment is highly impossible.
			 The participants are therefore requested to show some patience. However, if you do not get your money within 
			 45 days after submitting working code, please get in touch with us - we shall be happy to assist you. 
			 If there are problems with the submitted code, naturally, there will be further delays.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    </string>
   
   	<string name="faqs"></string>
     
    <string name="lab_migration1">
	    Lab Migration aims to migrate labs that use proprietary software (e.g. OrCAD, PSpice) to a Free 
	    and Open Source Software (FOSS) only lab. We recommend the use of Oscad as it offers the same 
	    capabilities and ease of use as any equivalent proprietary EDA tool for circuit design, simulation, 
	    analysis and PCB design without having to pay a huge amount of money to procure licenses. We 
	    invite students and faculty from all Engineering Colleges to come forward and take part in this 
	    project.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Lab Migration team helps in the following ways:
    </string>
    <string name="lab_migration2">
        - Provide suggestions on the different ways Oscad can be implemented in the laboratory. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
        - Coordinate the migration of the lab to FOSS only laboratory. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
        - Provide solutions to the lab\'s problem statements. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
        - Conduct Oscad workshops free of cost.
    </string>
    <string name="lab_migration3">
        Learn how to submit a proposal here ­ <![CDATA[<a href="http://oscad.in/lab_migration/proposal">http://oscad.in/lab_migration/proposal</a>]]>. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
        We can also be reached directly at <![CDATA[<a href=\'mailto:labmigration@oscad.in\'>labmigration@oscad.in</a>]]>.&lt;br /&gt;
    </string>
    <string name="lab_migration4">
        Teachers/Professors/Students from educational institutions across the country can participate in the Lab Migration project. 
        The participation procedure is different for college teachers and students.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
        For College Teachers:
    </string>
    <string name="lab_migration5">
		1. Fill the Lab Migration proposal form provided at 
		<![CDATA[<a href="http://oscad.in/lab_migration/proposal/">http://oscad.in/lab_migration/proposal</a>]]>. 
		To access the above mentioned page, please log in to the website. 
		If you do not have a login account, please register here. 
		In the proposal form provide details about your lab course, 
		problem statements, titles of the exercises.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
	
		2. In the proposal form, choose between providing the solutions for the problems 
		mentioned in the proposal form by yourself or floating the problems to the Lab Migration Project community.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
	
		3. In case you are not providing the Oscad solutions, other community members 
		can propose to provide the Oscad solutions for the problems mentioned in your Lab Migration proposal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
	
		4. While filling the proposal form, select whether you want the Oscad solutions of the 
		problems mentioned in the proposal form to be made available for other members to view/download/use.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
	
		5. Once you have filled all the required fields, submit the form. On successful 
		submission of the proposal form, you will receive a notification e-mail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
	
		6. You will receive an approval/disapproval mail within few days. If you have chosen to 
		submit the Oscad solutions yourself, you can start creating projects in Oscad for the 
		assigned lab and upload the codes on the interface.
    </string>
    <string name="lab_migration6">
        For Students and other Community Members:
    </string>
    <string name="lab_migration7">
        1. Visit the page <![CDATA[<a href="http://oscad.in/lab_migration/open_proposal/">http://oscad.in/lab_migration/open_proposal</a>]]>. Please log in to access 
        the above mentioned page. If you do not have a login account, 
        please visit <![CDATA[<a href="http://oscad.in/user/register/">http://oscad.in/user/register</a>]]> to create an account. 
        This page will have a list of lab problems for which Oscad solutions are to be provided.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

		2. Select the lab for which you want to provide the solution. This you can do by 
		clicking on the "Apply" button next to the "Title of the Lab". 
		This action will take you to "Lab Migration Solution Proposal" form.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
		
		3. Once you submit the form, we will approve it taking into consideration your proposal and other proposals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
		
		4. You will receive an email informing whether your proposal has been approved or disapproved. 
		Once your proposal is approved, you can start creating the projects in Oscad for the assigned lab 
		and upload the codes on the interface.
    </string>
    <string name="lab_migration8">
        Note:
        Any user who provides solutions for a lab course, can only work on one lab at a time. 
        They can move on to another lab once the current lab\'s solutions have been provided.&lt;br /&gt;
    </string>
    <string name="lab_migration9">
        The honorarium details for Lab Migration are as follows:
    </string>
    <string name="lab_migration10">
		- Rs.2000/- for the Faculty- For submitting the lab proposal and providing an undertaking 
			that the Oscad solutions provided for the lab will be used for 2 years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    	- Rs.2000/- for the HoD- For providing an undertaking that the Oscad solutions 
    		provided for the lab will be used for 2 years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    	- Rs.1000/- for the Faculty- For reviewing the code that has been provided to the teacher.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    	- Rs.4000/- for the Solution Provider- For providing solutions to the lab\'s exercises.
    		The faculty can also submit the solutions to the lab exercises.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    	- Rs.1000/- for the Principal of the college.
     </string>
    <string-array name="questions_array1">
        <item>1. What is Textbook Companion?</item>
        <item>2. Which book can I choose?</item>
        <item>3. What is the minimum number of examples a book should have?</item>
        <item>4. Who is eligible for internship?</item>
        <item>5. What are the prerequisites for applying for the internship?</item>
        <item>6. What is the deadline for the internship?</item>
        <item>7. Can the internship be cancelled if it is allotted to me? Has it ever been cancelled for anybody?</item>
        <item>8. What is the role of the teacher?</item>
        <item>9. Is it necessary to have a mentor?</item>
        <item>10. Does my teacher have to formally inform her/his HoD?</item>
        <item>11. Can the same teacher mentor more than one student?</item>
        <item>12. Can more than one student work on the same book?</item>
        <item>13. Is it necessary to come to IIT Bombay for completing the internship?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="answers_array1">
        <item>The Textbook Companion aims to generate an online collection of Oscad 
            based circuit simulations for worked out examples and select 
            exercise problems from standard textbooks.</item>
        <item>Any book containing solved circuit analysis and circuit simulation examples 
            can be chosen for creating TBC. However, the applicant has to ensure that the 
            proposed book has not already been completed or is being completed currently by 
            any other intern. The list of completed books and books in progress is available 
            on the website. In case the book has already been completed or is being worked 
            upon by another intern, then the book proposal will be rejected. Also note that 
            the responsibility of ensuring such a scenario does not arise bears with the intern 
            and/or his teacher as per the undertaking form.</item>
       	<item>The book can have any number of examples and payment is based on per example basis. 
       	    Please note that you should complete all the examples in the chosen book.</item>
       	<item>Students pursuing graduation from various colleges are eligible for this internship. 
       	    Please note that the internship will also involve a teacher of the student 
       	    (from the same college) who has taught the subject for at least one or two years. 
       	    The teacher is expected to guide the student through the internship and will be 
       	    responsible for the student\'s submissions.</item>
       	<item>There are no prerequisites for applying for the internship. 
       	    The student should be comfortable with Oscad software environment. 
       	    Spoken Tutorials are available for self-­learning of Oscad software. 
       	    Please visit: http://www.oscad.in/resources/tutorials</item>
       	<item>The internship should be completed within 3 months after proposing the book. 
       	    The simulation exercises can be uploaded in multiple groups (e.g. chapter wise) 
       	    before the deadline. Applicants may contact us at textbook[at]oscad[dot]in, 
       	    if the deadline needs to be changed. Please note that the extension of the 
       	    deadline for the completion of the internship will be considered only in case of 
       	    genuine reasons.</item>
       	<item>Yes. Refusal to meet the deadline, poor performance and badgering the 
       	    Oscad team are some of the reasons as to why the internship could be cancelled. 
       	    No partial payment will be made in such a case.</item>
       	<item>The teacher is expected to guide the intern during the internship and will bear 
       	    the responsibility for the student\'s submissions and undertakings.</item>
       	<item>Yes. It is necessary to have a mentor. However, if you are do not have a mentor 
       	    in such cases, please inform us by e-mail <![CDATA[<a href=\'mailto:textbook-companion@oscad.in\'>textbookcompanion@oscad.in</a>]]>.
			Please note: in case you do not have a mentor, the remuneration meant for 
			the mentor will not be paid to the intern.</item>
       	<item>Although it isn’t necessary to inform the HOD, the teacher is advised to do so. 
       	    If the internship is part of some academic credit criterion, then it is mandatory.</item>
       	<item>Yes, the same teacher can mentor more than one student. 
       	    The teacher will have to submit separate undertaking forms for each student being mentored.</item>
       	<item>No, more than one student cannot work on the same book.</item>
       	<item>No, There is no need to come to IIT Bombay at any phase of the internship. 
       	    All the correspondence will be carried out via e­mails and/or postal services.</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="questions_array2">
        <item>1. How many books can I propose?</item>
        <item>2. Can I mail and ask if a book can be submitted for the book proposal?</item>
        <item>3. Can I mail my book proposal?</item>
        <item>4. Can I propose a book that has been completed or is under progress as a different edition?</item>
        <item>5. Do I need to know Oscad before I submit my book proposal?</item>
        <item>6. How many days do I have to submit the temporary allotment code?</item>
        <item>7. Can I refer to some solved examples as reference?</item>
        <item>8. Can I use some other computing package for creating TBC?</item>
        <item>9. How many days does it take to get a temporary and final allotment?</item>
        <item>10. When can I start the simulation exercises?</item>
        <item>11. I have completed solving all the examples in the entire textbook. What do I do now?</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="answers_array2">
        <item>Initially, an applicant can propose 3 books. One of the proposed books will 
            then be allotted for creating Textbook companion. However, if a student is 
            currently working on a particular book, then no other book should be proposed 
            until the previously allotted book has been completed successfully.</item>
        <item>Before you mail us please check the http://www.oscad.in/Completed_Books 
            and http://www.oscad.in/Books_Progress to get an idea as to whether 
            the book can be suggested.</item>
        <item>No, please use the book proposal form (http://www.oscad.in/proposal) to submit your proposal.</item>
        <item>No, you cannot propose a book that has either been completed or is under progress as a different edition.</item>
        <item>Yes, you need to learn Oscad to submit the temporary allotment solutions. 
            Spoken Tutorials are available for self-­learning of Oscad software. 
            Please visit: http://oscad.in/resources/tutorials</item>
        <item>7­ to 10 days depending on the book and number of examples.</item>
        <item>Yes, the solved examples for completed books under TBC 
            activity are available for free downloading. 
            The solved examples can be referred if needed.</item>
        <item>We encourage you to use Oscad. For use of any other open source software 
            package, contact us at <![CDATA[<a href=\'mailto:textbook-companion@oscad.in\'>textbookcompanion@oscad.in</a>]]>.</item>
        <item>It takes three days to get a temporary allotment from the day you submit 
            your book proposal. Further, it may take another ten days from the day you 
            submit the temporary allotment code, to get the final allotment. 
            Please contact us only if you haven\'t heard from us in ten days.</item>
        <item>The simulation exercises can be started as soon as the book proposed by you is approved 
            and book allotment is confirmed. The confirmation will be communicated via an automated e­mail.</item>
        <item>Please contact the Oscad team at <![CDATA[<a href=\'mailto:textbook-companion@oscad.in\'>textbookcompanion@oscad.in</a>]]> 
            and let them know that your solutions are completed.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    
    
    <string-array name="questions_array3">
        <item>1. When do I submit the internship forms?</item>
        <item>2. Is there a deadline for submitting the internship forms?</item>
        <item>3. What is the procedure for acquiring certificates/honorarium?</item>
        <item>4. How long does it take to receive my Honorarium?</item>
        <item>5. Why is there a delay in my Honorarium payment?</item>
        <item>6. What about intellectual rights of the TBC?</item>
        <item>7. Can I propose more books after completion?</item>
        <item>8. I have finished one or more textbook companions already. Is there any other activity I can participate in?</item>
        <item>9. Where do I get a one ­rupee revenue stamp? How does a revenue stamp look like?</item>
        <item>10. Whom do I contact in case I still have a doubt?</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="answers_array3">
        <item>You can submit the forms once the review for the examples 
            of the entire textbook has been completed and your solutions has been approved.</item>
        <item>There is no definite deadline for submitting the internship forms.</item>
        <item>The uploaded simulation solutions will be reviewed and once the solutions 
            are found satisfactory the applicant will be informed. 
            The intern has to mail the forms after completion of the review. 
            The candidate should then mail ALL the internship related forms AFTER 
            filling the appropriate details to IIT Bombay to the following address:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			Prof. Kannan Moudgalya,&lt;br /&gt;
			Department of Chemical Engineering,&lt;br /&gt;
			IIT Bombay, Powai - 400076&lt;br /&gt;
			Mumbai&lt;br /&gt;
			Ph: 022 2576 4133&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

			Please write "Textbook Companion" on top of the envelope. 
			The certificates will then be sent via post after all the duly filled forms are received.</item>
        <item>If you do not get your money within 45 days after submitting working code, please get in touch with us ­ 
            we shall be happy to assist you. If there are problems with the submitted code, 
            naturally, there will be further delays.</item>
        <item>On submission of a Textbook Companion, the review process 
            involves several checks including but not limited to:-&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			a. Incorrect simulation output.&lt;br /&gt;
			b. Completeness of the book ­missing parts (or) sections of the solutions.&lt;br /&gt;
			c. Plagiarism.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			
			In this regards, we test EVERY solution of EVERY participant thoroughly. 
			As there are many participants involved in this activity, 
			this verification process takes considerable amount of time. Moreover, 
			dispatch of Government money requires approvals from the Dean\'s Office, Accounts 
			Office, etc., which also takes some time. Due to the above listed reasons, 
			immediate acceptance of a Textbook Companion and processing of payment gets delayed.</item>
        <item>The copyrights for TBC will be handed to FOSSEE Project. 
            The name of creator of TBC and teacher will be published on the website. 
            The TBC will be available for free downloading on Oscad website.</item>
        <item>Yes, you are welcome to propose more books. Please encourage your friends to take part in this internship.</item>
        <item>You can take part in the Lab Migration Activity 
            (http://oscad.in/lab-migration-project) and the Textbook Companion for 
            Python (http://fossee.in/deliverables)</item>
        <item>You can buy a one rupee revenue stamp from the Post Office. 
            Here is a scan of a fully filled internship form 
            ­http://oscad.in/files/download/forms/example­filled­receipt.pdf</item>
        <item>You can contact the Oscad team at <![CDATA[<a href=\'mailto:textbook-companion@oscad.in\'>textbookcompanion@oscad.in</a>]]>.</item>
        
    </string-array>
    
    <string name="space">Oscad Examples (469 KB)<![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;]]></string>
</resources>
